Xian-Hao (Harry) Liao Audiovisual Designer

renogordondj@gmail.com San Jose, CA +1.857.693.8315 xian-hao-liao.com

Creative professional with 2+ years of experience in webpage development, designing layouts for promotional materials and utilizing 3D modeling skills for UI UX prototyping seeking a design 2023 summer internship position in California.

Work Experience

MassArt / Marketing Graduate Assistantship

09/2022 - Present, Boston, MA, U.S.

Future House Music / Freelance 3D Artist

05/2022 - 07/2022, Amsterdam, Netherlands, Remote

Design and adjustment to 3D Scenes using C4D. Discuss back and forth with clients to finalize artwork. Released on Spotify, and YouTube with 10K+ views and 1K+ subscribers.

ABC Design.tw / Graphic Designer

07/2021 - 05/2022, Taichung City, Taiwan

Represent ABC Design.de's products in Taiwan. Rolled out new product ideas including social media engagements and marketing materials which launched to over 150 local retail stores. Facilitated cross-departmental work and served as the go-to person of the design department. Coordinated with suppliers on material decisions and color corrections to support new product launches.

Bonneboutique Shop / Product Photographer

03/2019 - 06/2020, Taichung City, Taiwan

Co-led the design and development of a new online store launched in July 2019. Conducted professional photoshoots, including scene preparations for products in the online store. Ran promotional events on social media and increased sales amount by 20%.

Jye Tsae Color Printing Co Ltd / Layout Designer

09/2016 - 05/2017, Taichung City, Taiwan

Accomplished over 100 client projects in design and layout of pre-press and printing in a team of 5. Assisted senior team members to demonstrate high-precision laser cutting and packaging to clients. Conceptualized client ideas and performed photo post-processing in Photoshop.

Education

MassArt / MFA DMI

Massachusetts College of Art and Design Master of Fine Arts, Dynamic Media Institute, Boston, MA MFA expected '24

NTCUST / BA CD

National Taichung University of Science and Technology Bachelor of Design, Commercial Design, Taichung City, Taiwan 09/2016-07/2020

Skills

Design: Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Lightroom, Mixamo, Cinema 4D, Octane Render, Capture One

Visuals Production: Adobe Premiere, After Effect, Final cut, Ableton Live, AVID Pro Tools, AVID Composer

Prototyping: Adobe XD, Figma, UI/UX, interactive flow with HTML/ CSS/ JS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, React JS, p5.js

Language: Mandarin / Native English / Professional Working Proficiency

Personal Projects

You Are Here Now Platform Project Main Developer, 09/2022 - 11/2022

Sunny Wang Celebrity Branding Project Graphic Designer, 07/2021 - 05/2022

NTCUST Youth Innovation Base Webpage Design Team Leader, 01/2020 - 06/2020

Reno Gordon DJ Music Video Video Producer, 08/2018 - 06/2020